(Penny:)Okay, well, it sounds like
things are gonna work out.
(Leonard:)Yeah. Yeah, it's all good.
Everything's gonna work out,
one way or another.
God, come on, Leonard.
(Penny:)You are entitled to try and make things
go the way you want them to.
(Leonard:)- Really?
- Yes.
(Penny:)You don't always have to go along
with what the woman wants.
(Steph:)Huh.
(Penny:)- What?
- Nothing. Just rethinking my whole life.
(Leonard:)Okay, here's the thing.
(Leonard:)I'm afraid that if I ask her to move out,
she'll just dump me.
Well, that's a chance you have to take.
(Penny:)I mean, look, if it's meant to be, it'll be.
(Leonard:)Very comforting.
(Leonard:)Okay, so, what do I say to her?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
What have women said to you...
(Penny:)...when they wanted
to slow a relationship down?
(Leonard:)I really like you,
but I wanna see how things go with Mark?